ILGWU Toronto Dressmakers Joint Council and Toronto Cloak Joint Board Records 5780/043
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Office Committee. Minutes., 1943-1949 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Office Committee. Minutes., 1950-1955 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Office Committee. Minutes. [folder 1 of 2], 1955-1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Office Committee. Minutes. [folder 2 of 2], 1955-1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Pressers. Minutes., 1942-1949 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Pressers. Minutes., 1950-1958 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Pressers. Minutes., 1952-1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Grievance Committee. Minutes., 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Membership Committee. Minutes., 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Election Objection Committee. Minutes., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Pressers. Minutes., 1936-1939 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Scope and Contents
  Yiddish
- Cutters. Minutes., 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Cutters. Minutes., 1944-1947 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Cutters. Minutes., 1947-1954 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Cutters. Minutes., 1954-1958 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Cutters. Minutes., 1957-1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- The Voice of Labor/La Voce del Lavoro. [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Italian
- The Voice of Labor/La Voce del Lavoro. [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- The Voice of Labor/La Voce del Lavoro. [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Correspondence., 1941-1965 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Form Letters (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 12)
- The Needle Worker. Vol. I, No.1- Vol. VI, No.5, 1950-1957 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Joint Board. Minutes., 1928-1930 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Joint Board. Minutes., 1930-1932 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Joint Board. Minutes., 1933-1935 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Joint Board. Minutes., 1934-1934 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Joint Board. Minutes., 1935-1937 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Joint Board. Minutes. [folder 1 of 2], 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Yiddish and English
- Joint Board. Minutes. [folder 2 of 2], 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Joint Board. Minutes. [folder 1 of 2], 1951-1953 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Joint Board. Minutes. [folder 2 of 2], 1951-1953 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Correspondence., 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Joint Board. Minutes. [folder 1 of 2], 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Joint Board. Minutes. [folder 2 of 2], 1945-1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Joint Board. Minutes. [folder 1 of 2], 1956-1959 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Joint Board. Minutes. [folder 2 of 2], 1956-1959 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Joint Board. Minutes. [folder 1 of 3], 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Joint Board. Minutes. [folder 2 of 3], 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Joint Board. Minutes. [folder 3 of 3], 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Joint Board. Minutes. [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Joint Board. Minutes. [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Joint Board. Minutes. [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1970 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Union Label [folder 1 of 2], 1961-1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Union Label [folder 2 of 2], 1961-1971 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- War Efforts Committee. Minutes., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Grievance Board. Minutes., 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Grievance Board. Minutes., 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Toronto Cloak and Suit Employees Sick Benefit Fund, 1946-1948 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Cutters. Minutes., 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Cutters. Minutes., 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Local 14. Minutes., 1931-1934 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Local 14. Minutes., 1934-1937 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Local 14. Minutes., 1952-1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Local 14. Minutes., 1965-1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Local 94. Minutes., 1941-1944 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Pressers Locals 68 and 92. Minutes., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Local 92. Minutes., 1934-1936 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Local 92. Minutes., 1963-1970 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Canadian Coordinating Conferences, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Canadian Coordinating Conferences, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Canadian Coordinating Conferences, 1942-1948 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Canadian Coordinating Conferences, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Canadian Coordinating Conferences, 1954-1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Canadian Trades and Labour Congress, 1954-1960 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Cases, 1953-1965 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Displaced Persons, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Dubinsky, David, 1931-1932 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Dubinsky, David, 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Dubinsky, David, 1935-1939 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Dubinsky, David, 1942-1966 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration of Toronto Cloak Makers Union, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Firms, 1941-1969 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Firms. Buchan-Sinclair Ltd. and Cole of California, 1946-1968 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Firms. Exquisite Form Brassiere Co., 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Firms. Myers Dress Co. Ltd., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Firms. Sport rite Junior Ltd., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Firms. Walter H. Harmon Ltd., 1965-1969 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Firms. Windsor Textile Co. Ltd., 1955-1957 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Farm and Bergstein, Barristers, Solicitors, Notaries, 1965-1970 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Fur Workers Union, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- General Office, 1933-1969 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- General Office, Auditing Dept., 1927-1956 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- General Office, Auditing Dept., 1933-1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Government Departments, 1932-1955 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Health and Welfare Dept., 1948-1967 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Health and Welfare Dept., 1968-1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Health, Welfare and Related Benefits [folder 1 of 7], 1950-1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Health, Welfare and Related Benefits [folder 2 of 7], 1950-1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Health, Welfare and Related Benefits [folder 3 of 7], 1950-1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Health, Welfare and Related Benefits [folder 4 of 7], 1950-1979 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Health, Welfare and Related Benefits [folder 5 of 7], 1950-1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Health, Welfare and Related Benefits [folder 6 of 7], 1950-1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Health, Welfare and Related Benefits [folder 7 of 7], 1950-1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Impartial Chairman, 1935-1951 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Impartial Chairman, 1951-1962 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Ladies' Cloak and Suit Industry, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Macks, Joe (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Magerman and Page, Barristers & Solicitors, 1962-1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Montreal Joint Council, 1932-1937 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Montreal Joint Council, 1938-1941 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Montreal Joint Council, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Montreal Joint Council, 1943-1950 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Montreal Joint Council, 1951-1954 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Montreal Joint Council, 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Montreal Joint Council, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Montreal Joint Council, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Montreal Joint Council and Dressmakers Joint Board, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Montreal Joint Council and Montreal Dressmakers Joint Board, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Montreal Joint Board, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Montreal Joint Council and Montreal Joint Board, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Montreal Joint Council and Montreal Joint Board, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Montreal Joint Council and Montreal Joint Board, 1944-1968 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Montreal Health, Welfare and Retirement, 1940-1970 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Ontario Federation of Labour, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Ontario Labour Relations Board, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Price Lists and Salary Lists, 1940-1959 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Price Lists [folder 1 of 3], 1940-1959 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Price Lists [folder 2 of 3], 1940-1959 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Price Lists [folder 3 of 3], 1940-1959 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Regional War Labour Board, Ontario, 1942-1946 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Retirement Fund, Toronto Cloak and Suit Industry, Montreal, 1948-1966 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Roebuck and Bagwell, Barristers, Solicitors & Notaries Public, 1931-1950 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Impartial Chairman [folder 1 of 2], 1935-1948 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Impartial Chairman [folder 2 of 2], 1935-1948 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Stulberg, Louis, 1936-1964 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Stulberg, Louis, 1965-1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Toronto Cloak Manufacturers Association, 1935-1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Toronto Dress and Sportswear Manufacturers Association, 1946-1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Union Label Campaign, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Windsor, Ontario, 1966-1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Winnipeg, Manitoba, 1934-1932 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Winnipeg, Manitoba, 1950-1958 (Box 11, Folder 8)